http://www.perlier.com/pages/privacy-policy

SHOP ALL ALLHOLIDAY SHOPNEWFAN FAVORITESSUBSCRIBE & SAVEBODY CARE SHOP BY CATEGORY BATH & SHOWER CREAMSBODY CREAMS & BUTTERSHANDS & FEET HAND CREAMSNAIL & CUTICLEFOOT CARELIQUID & BAR SOAPSHAIR CARE SHAMPOOCONDITIONERS & SERUMSBODY WATERSSHOP BY KEY INGREDIENT HONEY ORGANIC ITALIAN HONEYSICILIAN BLACK BEE HONEY + ROYAL JELLYORGANIC ITALIAN HONEY, ALMOND CREAM + BEESWAXALMONDS PIZZUTA ALMOND OIL, ALMOND MILK + VITAMIN EWHITE ALMOND OIL + MILKSHEA PURE ORGANIC SHEA BUTTERPURE ORGANIC SHEA BUTTER + ARGAN OILHEMPOLIVE OILPOMEGRANATESICILIAN CITRUSSHOP BY NEED HYDRATE & MOISTURIZELIFT & FIRMANTI-AGINGSENSITIVE SKINSHOP BY COLLECTION AGRUMARIUMHONEY MIELIMPERIAL HONEYWHITE HONEYGOLDEN ALMONDMELOGRANOOLIVARIUMDOUBLE LATTESKINCARE SHOP BY CATEGORY FACE CLEANSERS & TONERSFACE SERUMS & OILSFACE MASKSEYE CREAMS & TREATMENTSNECK & CHESTLIP BALMS & MASKSSHOP BY KEY INGREDIENT HEMPBLACK RICEFRESH ROYAL JELLYROSE OF JERICHOSHOP BY COLLECTION PLATINUM BLACK RICEHYDRO-ZONEROYAL ELIXIRSHOP BY NEEDFRAGRANCESSPECIAL OFFERS HOLIDAY SAVINGSPLUMPING LIP GLOSSES JUST $6,25HONEY FLORAL BODY CARE UP TO 60% OFFMOISTURIZING BODY SPRAYS AS LOW AS $9.90SUBSCRIBE & SAVEABOUT OUR STORY ABOUT USWHERE IT BEGANOUR PROCESSLA CARIGNANAOUR INGREDIENTS KEY INGREDIENTSHONEYSHEA BUTTEROLIVE OILWHITE ALMONDPOMEGRANATESICILIAN BLACK BEE HONEYROYAL JELLYSHEA BUTTERARGAN OIL'GOLDEN' AVOLA ALMONDHOW OUR HONEY IS MADELEARN MORE ABOUT OUR CITRUSWHITE ALMOND ORCHARDSWHERE WE SOURCE OUR SHEA BUTTERTHE LAVENDER FIELDS
0
items in your cart
$0.00
total cart value
Your Cart
Continue Shopping
FREE SHIPPING WITH $100+ ORDERS
Shop All
Purpose
When you provide information through Perlier.com (the "Site"), we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Your visit to the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Please note that this Privacy Policy governs only information provided to Perlier.com.
Collection of Personally Identifiable Information by Perlier.com
We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you decide to complete a user registration form or online survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number), age group, gender and product and/or cosmetic concerns, and the brands and products you use. If you decide to place an order, we will also need to know your delivery and billing address, credit card number and expiration date. To protect your personal information, users registering at the Site must also enter a user name/email address and password. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information. When you submit your personally identifiable information on the Site, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
Automatic Collection Of Anonymous Information
When you visit the Perlier website, like when you visit most other websites, certain anonymous information about your visit is automatically logged, which may include information about the type of browser you use, the server name and IP address through which you access the internet (such as "aol.com" or "msn.com"), the date and time you access the site, the pages you access while at the Perlier.com website, and the internet address of the website, if any, from which you linked directly to the Perlier.com site. This information is not personally identifiable.
Children's Privacy
This website is directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. If you are under 13 years of age, you may browse our Site. However, you may not provide personal information to us. For example, you cannot register or make a purchase. This Site is not designed for children and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any children under 13.
Security
Perlier.com maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personally identifiable information. If transactions are offered on the site, transaction information is transmitted to and from Perlier.com in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Perlier.com restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception.
Choice/Opt-Out
In order to provide service to you, Perlier.com will send you communications related to your transactions, security or the administration of its website. From time to time, Perlier.com may also wish to send you other messages or updates about Perlier.com, or our promotions and other activities. If you do not wish to receive non-transaction/security related communications from Perlier.com please send an email containing your request to customer service email info@perlier.com or call us at 877-737-5353.
Cookies
The Perlier's website may place a "cookie" on your computer in order to allow you to use the website and to personalize your experience. A "cookie" is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow Perlier.com to recognize your computer while you are on its website and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the website. Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of this website.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Perlier.com reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Perlier.com will post a notice on its homepage and a link to the new policy.
Contacting Us
If you have questions about this privacy statement, the information practices of Perlier.com or your dealings with Perlier.com, please contact Perlier by phone at 732.585.6390 or email info@perlier.com.
